let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is Boyle's Law?",
    answer: "The volume of a constant-temperature gas is inversely proportional to the pressure at which it is measured.",
    options: [
     "The volume of a constant-temperature gas is directly proportional to the pressure at which it is measured.",
     "The volume of a gas increases with increasing pressure.",
     "The volume of a gas decreases with increasing pressure.",
     "The volume of a gas remains constant regardless of pressure."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How does the pressure of a gas change when its volume is reduced?",
    answer: "It increases.",
    options: [
     "It decreases.",
     "It remains constant.",
     "It is not affected by volume changes.",
     "It follows a random pattern."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What happens to the pressure of a gas when its volume is increased?",
    answer: "It decreases.",
    options: [
     "It increases.",
     "It remains constant.",
     "It is not affected by volume changes.",
     "It follows a random pattern."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What type of graph represents the relationship between pressure and volume according to Boyle's Law?",
    answer: "The graph of 1P/1P versus V.",
    options: [
     "The graph of P versus V.",
     "The graph of P versus 1/V.",
     "The graph of P versus T.",
     "The graph of P versus n."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Are pressure and volume directly proportional to each other?",
    answer: "No, pressure and volume are inversely proportional to each other according to Boyle's Law.",
    options: [
     "Yes, pressure and volume are directly proportional to each other according to Boyle's Law.",
     "No, pressure and volume are not related to each other.",
     "Yes, pressure and volume have a linear relationship.",
     "Yes, pressure and volume have a quadratic relationship."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How can the relationship between pressure and volume be expressed mathematically?",
    answer: "P1V1 = P2V2",
    options: [
     "P1V1 + P2V2 = k",
     "P1V1 / P2V2 = k",
     "P1V1 - P2V2 = k",
     "P1V1 * P2V2 = k"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How accurate is estimating pressure using the P-V graph?",
    answer: "It provides an approximate value.",
    options: [
     "It provides an exact value.",
     "It is not a reliable method.",
     "It provides a range of values.",
     "It provides a negative value."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How accurate is estimating pressure using the 1P/1P versus V graph?",
    answer: "It also provides an approximate value.",
    options: [
     "It provides an exact value.",
     "It is not a reliable method.",
     "It provides a range of values.",
     "It provides a negative value."
    ]
  },
 {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the relationship described by Avogadro's Law?",
    answer: "The volume and number of moles of a gas are directly proportional if pressure and temperature remain constant.",
    options: [
     "The volume and number of moles of a gas are inversely proportional if pressure and temperature remain constant.",
     "The pressure and number of moles of a gas are directly proportional if volume and temperature remain constant.",
     "The pressure and number of moles of a gas are inversely proportional if volume and temperature remain constant.",
     "The pressure and temperature of a gas are directly proportional if volume and number of moles remain constant."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "According to Avogadro's Law, what happens to the volume of a gas if the number of moles is doubled?",
    answer: "The volume will also double.",
    options: [
     "The volume will be halved.",
     "The volume will remain the same.",
     "The volume will decrease by a factor of four.",
     "The volume will also double, but with an opposite sign."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which equation represents Avogadro's Law?",
    answer: "V1/n1 = V2/n2",
    options: [
     "P1V1 = P2V2",
     "P1/n1 = P2/n2",
     "P1V1/T1 = P2V2/T2",
     "P1/T1 = P2/T2"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What does Avogadro's Law state about the relationship between volume and number of moles?",
    answer: "They have a direct proportionality.",
    options: [
     "They have an inverse proportionality.",
     "They have a quadratic relationship.",
     "They have no relationship.",
     "They have a direct proportionality, but with an opposite sign."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "In Avogadro's Law, what condition must remain constant?",
    answer: "Pressure and temperature",
    options: [
     "Volume and temperature",
     "Volume and pressure",
     "Number of moles and pressure",
     "Number of moles and temperature"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which gas law describes the relationship between pressure and number of moles?",
    answer: "The ideal gas law",
    options: [
     "Boyle's Law",
     "Charles's Law",
     "Gay-Lussac's Law",
     "The ideal gas law"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What is the mathematical expression for Avogadro's Law?",
    answer: "V/n = k",
    options: [
     "V * n = k",
     "V + n = k",
     "V - n = k",
     "V / n = k"
    ]
  },
]